{
    "exam_metadata": {
        "layout": "exam",
        "title": "Practice Exam 16",
        "exam_id": 16,
        "courseName": "AWS Cloud Practitioner",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "tags": [
            "aws",
            "cloud"
        ],
        "description": "Introduction exam",
        "level": "FOUNDATIONAL"
    },
    "questions": [
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "question_text": "Which of the following provides the ability to share the cost benefits of Reserved Instances across AWS accounts?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Linked accounts and consolidated billing",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost Explorer between AWS accounts"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Linked accounts and consolidated billing"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) Reserved Instance Utilization Report"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 Instance Usage Report between AWS accounts"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "question_text": "A company has multiple AWS accounts and wants to simplify and consolidate its billing process. <br/>Which AWS service will achieve this?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Organizations",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost and Usage Reports"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Organizations"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost Explorer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Budgets"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "question_text": "A company is designing an application hosted in a single AWS Region serving end-users spread across the world. The company wants to provide the end-users low latency access to the application data. <br/> Which of the following services will help fulfill this requirement?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon CloudFront",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Route 53 global DNS"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) transfer acceleration"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "question_text": "Which of the following deployment models enables customers to fully trade their capital IT expenses for operational expenses?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Cloud",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "On-premises"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Hybrid"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Cloud"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Platform as a service"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 6,
            "question_text": "How is asset management on AWS easier than asset management in a physical data center?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS performs infrastructure discovery scans on the customer's behalf.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS provides a Configuration Management Database that users can maintain."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS performs infrastructure discovery scans on the customer's behalf."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 automatically generates an asset report and places it in the customer's specified Amazon S3 bucket."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Users can gather asset metadata reliably with a few API calls."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 7,
            "question_text": "What feature of Amazon RDS helps to create globally redundant databases?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Cross-Region read replicas",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Snapshots"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Automatic patching and updating"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Cross-Region read replicas"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Provisioned IOPS"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 8,
            "question_text": "Using AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) to grant access only to the resources needed to perform a task is a concept known as:",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "least privilege access.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "restricted access."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "as-needed access."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "least privilege access."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "token access."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 9,
            "question_text": "Which methods can be used to identify AWS costs by departments? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Create separate accounts for each department. | Use tags to associate each instance with a particular department.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Enable multi-factor authentication for the AWS account root user."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Create separate accounts for each department."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Use Reserved Instances whenever possible."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Use tags to associate each instance with a particular department."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Pay bills using purchase orders."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 10,
            "question_text": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, customer responsibilities include which one of the following?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Configuring the operating system, network, and firewall.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Securing the hardware, software, facilities, and networks that run all products and services."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Providing certificates, reports, and other documentation directly to AWS customers under NDA."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Configuring the operating system, network, and firewall."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Obtaining industry certifications and independent third-party attestations."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 11,
            "question_text": "Which managed AWS service provides real-time guidance on AWS security best practices?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS X-Ray"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudWatch"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Systems Manager"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 12,
            "question_text": "Which feature adds elasticity to Amazon EC2 instances to handle the changing demand for workloads?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Resource groups"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Lifecycle policies"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Application Load Balancer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 13,
            "question_text": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, customers are responsible for which aspects of security in the cloud? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "Encryption management | Firewall management",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Visualization management"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Hardware management"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Encryption management"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Facilities management"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Firewall management"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 14,
            "question_text": "Which AWS hybrid storage service enables on-premises applications to seamlessly use AWS Cloud storage through standard file-storage protocols?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Storage Gateway",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Snowball"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Storage Gateway"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Snowball Edge"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 15,
            "question_text": "What is a responsibility of AWS in the shared responsibility model?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Updating the firmware on the underlying EC2 hosts.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Updating the network ACLs to block traffic to vulnerable ports."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Patching operating systems running on Amazon EC2 instances."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Updating the firmware on the underlying EC2 hosts."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Updating the security group rules to block traffic to the vulnerable ports."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 16,
            "question_text": "Which architectural principle is used when deploying an Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) instance in Multiple Availability Zone mode?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Design for failure.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Implement loose coupling."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Design for failure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Automate everything that can be automated."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Use services, not servers."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 17,
            "question_text": "What does it mean to grant least privilege to AWS IAM users?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "It is granting only the permissions required to perform a given task.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "It is granting permissions to a single user only."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "It is granting permissions using AWS IAM policies only."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "It is granting AdministratorAccess policy permissions to trustworthy users."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "It is granting only the permissions required to perform a given task."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 18,
            "question_text": "What is a benefit of loose coupling as a principle of cloud architecture design?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "It prevents cascading failures between different components.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "It facilitates low-latency request handling."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "It allows applications to have dependent workflows."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "It prevents cascading failures between different components."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "It allows companies to focus on their physical data center operations."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 19,
            "question_text": "A director has been tasked with investigating hybrid cloud architecture. The company currently accesses AWS over the public internet.<br/>Which service will facilitate private hybrid connectivity?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Direct Connect",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) NAT Gateway"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) Transfer Acceleration"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Web Application Firewall (AWS WAF)"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 20,
            "question_text": "A company's web application currently has tight dependencies on underlying components, so when one component fails the entire web application fails. <br> Applying which AWS Cloud design principle will address the current design issue?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Focusing on decoupling components by isolating them and ensuring individual components can function when other components fail.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Implementing elasticity, enabling the application to scale up or scale down as demand changes."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Enabling several EC2 instances to run in parallel to achieve better performance."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Focusing on decoupling components by isolating them and ensuring individual components can function when other components fail."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Doubling EC2 computing resources to increase system fault tolerance."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 21,
            "question_text": "How can a customer increase security to AWS account logons? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Enable Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) | Configure a strong password policy",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Configure AWS Certificate Manager"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Enable Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Use Amazon Cognito to manage access"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Configure a strong password policy"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Enable AWS Organizations"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 22,
            "question_text": "What AWS service would be used to centrally manage AWS access across multiple accounts?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Organizations",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Service Catalog"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Organizations"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 23,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service can a customer use to set up an alert notification when the account is approaching a particular dollar amount?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Budgets",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost and Usage reports"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Budgets"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost Explorer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 24,
            "question_text": "What can users access from AWS Artifact?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS security and compliance documents",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS security and compliance documents"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "A download of configuration management details for all AWS resources"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Training materials for AWS services"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "A security assessment of the applications deployed in the AWS Cloud"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 25,
            "question_text": "Which is the MINIMUM AWS Support plan that provides designated Technical Account Managers?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Enterprise",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Enterprise"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Business"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Developer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Basic"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 26,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is an AWS Well-Architected Framework design principle related to reliability?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Ability to recover from failure",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Deployment to a single Availability Zone"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Ability to recover from failure"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Design for cost optimization"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Perform operations as code"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 27,
            "question_text": "Which type of AWS storage is ephemeral and is deleted when an instance is stopped or terminated?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon EC2 instance store",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EBS"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 instance store"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EFS"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 28,
            "question_text": "What is an advantage of using the AWS Cloud over a traditional on-premises solution?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Users do not have to guess about future capacity needs.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Users do not have to guess about future capacity needs."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Users can utilize existing hardware contracts for purchases."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Users can fix costs no matter what their traffic is."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Users can avoid audits by using reports from AWS."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 29,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is an AWS-managed compute service?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Lambda",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon SWF"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Lambda"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Aurora"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 30,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is an important architectural principle when designing cloud applications?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Design for failure",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Store data and backups in the same region."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Design tightly coupled system components."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Avoid multi-threading."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Design for failure"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 31,
            "question_text": "Which mechanism allows developers to access AWS services from application code?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Software Development Kit",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Software Development Kit"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Management Console"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodePipeline"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 32,
            "question_text": "Which Amazon EC2 pricing model is the MOST cost efficient for an uninterruptible workload that runs once a year for 24 hours?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "On-Demand Instances",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "On-Demand Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Reserved Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Spot Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Dedicated Instances"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 33,
            "question_text": "Which of the following services is a MySQL-compatible database that automatically grows storage as needed?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Aurora",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) for MySQL"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Lightsail"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Aurora"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 34,
            "question_text": "Which Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) feature enables users to connect two VPCs together?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon VPC peering",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon VPC endpoints"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) ClassicLink"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon VPC peering"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 35,
            "question_text": "Which service's PRIMARY purpose is software version control?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS CodeCommit",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CodeStar"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Cognito"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodeCommit"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 36,
            "question_text": "A company is considering migrating its applications to AWS. The company wants to compare the cost of running the workload on-premises to running the equivalent workload on the AWS platform. <br/>Which tool can be used to perform this comparison?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Billing and Cost Management console"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Cost Explorer"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 37,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides a secure, fast, and cost-effective way to migrate or transport exabyte-scale datasets into AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Snowmobile",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Batch"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Snowball"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Migration Hub"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Snowmobile"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 38,
            "question_text": "Which of the following BEST describe the AWS pricing model? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "Pay-as-you-go | Variable cost",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Fixed-term"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Pay-as-you-go"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Colocation"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Planned"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Variable cost"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 39,
            "question_text": "Which load balancer types are available with Elastic Load Balancing (ELB)? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "Classic Load Balancers | Application Load Balancers",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Public load balancers with AWS Application Auto Scaling capabilities"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "F5 Big-IP and Citrix NetScaler load balancers"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Classic Load Balancers"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Cross-zone load balancers with public and private IPs"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Application Load Balancers"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 40,
            "question_text": "Why should a company choose AWS instead of a traditional data center?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS does not require long-term contracts and provides a pay-as-you-go model.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS provides users with full control over the underlying resources."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS does not require long-term contracts and provides a pay-as-you-go model."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS offers edge locations in every country, supporting global reach."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS has no limits on the number of resources that can be created."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 41,
            "question_text": "Which solution provides the FASTEST application response times to frequently accessed data to users in multiple AWS Regions?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon CloudFront to edge locations",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudTrail across multiple Availability Zones"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront to edge locations"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudFormation in multiple regions"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "A virtual private gateway over AWS Direct Connect"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 42,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides a self-service portal for on-demand access to AWS compliance reports?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Artifact",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Certificate Manager"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Inspector"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Artifact"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 43,
            "question_text": "Which of the following AWS services can be used to run a self-managed database?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2)",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Route 53"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS X-Ray"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Snowmobile"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2)"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 44,
            "question_text": "What exclusive benefit is provided to users with Enterprise Support?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Access to a Technical Account Manager",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Access to a Technical Project Manager"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Access to a Technical Account Manager"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Access to a Cloud Support Engineer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Access to a Solutions Architect"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 45,
            "question_text": "How can a user protect against AWS service disruptions if a natural disaster affects an entire geographic area?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Deploy applications across multiple AWS Regions.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Deploy applications across multiple Availability Zones within an AWS Region."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Use a hybrid cloud computing deployment model within the geographic area."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Deploy applications across multiple AWS Regions."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Store application artifacts using AWS Artifact and replicate them across multiple AWS Regions."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 46,
            "question_text": "How does AWS MOST effectively reduce computing costs for a growing start-up company?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "It provides on-demand resources for peak usage.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "It provides on-demand resources for peak usage."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "It automates the provisioning of individual developer environments."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "It automates customer relationship management."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "It implements a fixed monthly computing budget."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 47,
            "question_text": "A startup is working on a new application that needs to go to market quickly. The application requirements may need to be adjusted in the near future. <br/> Which of the following is a characteristic of the AWS Cloud that would meet this specific need?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Agility",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Elasticity"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Reliability"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Performance"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Agility"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 48,
            "question_text": "Which AWS Support plan provides a full set of AWS Trusted Advisor checks?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Enterprise and Business Support",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Business and Developer Support"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Business and Basic Support"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Enterprise and Developer Support"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Enterprise and Business Support"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 49,
            "question_text": "Which of the following services have Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) mitigation features? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS WAF | Amazon CloudFront",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS WAF"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon DynamoDB"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Inspector"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 50,
            "question_text": "When building a cloud Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) model, which cost elements should be considered for workloads running on AWS? (Choose three.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, C, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Compute costs | Storage costs | Data transfer costs",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Compute costs"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Facilities costs"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Storage costs"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Data transfer costs"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Network infrastructure costs"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "F",
                    "option_text": "Hardware lifecycle costs"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}